Giovanni Paul-Sodipo

mailto:paulsodipo@yahoo.com

09090073211

Personal Summary:

A highly organized, detail-oriented and technically minded BSC pursuing Computer Science Student, with intermediate level of experience in the computing, marketing and media sectors, seeking to obtain professional experience in a facility where my skills can be honed and utilized.

I have 3+ years - MERN freelance front-end development, 2+ years - Web3 development, 2+ years - Meta community manager as well as certifications from LinkedIn, sololearn, meta (Facebook) and google. On a personal level, I possess an outgoing, calm and positive multitasking attitude, proficient communication and teamwork skills, and I am more than willing to learn new skills. I will like to join an ambitious company that is looking to recruit a talented Computer operator with potential.

Professional History:

Student Paddy

Ambassador/Junior Web Developer Apr 2022 - current Maintenance and modify necessary data on the website

Google Developers Community (Afe Babalola University Chapter)

Public Relations Manager Feb 2021 - Sep 2021

I brought awareness to the campaign of the benefits and requirements to be a google student developer

Reddington Hospital

Customer Care/Information Technology Staff Jul 2020 - Jan 2021 Nigeria

SM PRODUCTIONS

Freelance Audio Engineer Jan 2019 - Sep 2020 Nigeria

I worked as the recording engineer, sound designer, producer and mix & mastering engineer here

BeelCT

Project Intern

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018

We worked on the installation of monitors and wiring of a security station in a well-known facility \mathbf{Key} **Skills/Competencies:**

Professional;

- Effective in the use of Microsoft Office software.
- Ability to build and deploy NeXT's, React.JS Web Apps.
- Intermediately skilled in MYSQL Developer
- Conversant with HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS.

Personal;

- Able to calmly persevere in tough and difficult situations.
- Being Detail-Oriented.
- Improving Customer Experience.
- Positive Attitude.
- Bilingual Customer Support.
- Time Management.
- Interpersonal Skills.
- As a sound designer/creative marketing strategist, I'm well aware of the importance and the significance of precision, time and punctuality and particularly, I have good sales and bargaining techniques.
- Good teamwork and communication skills.

Education:

BEng Computer Science Afe Babalola University, Ekiti. September 2020 till date.

Modules: Programming, Business Analysis, Systems Information, Applied Math's, Statistics Language, HTML, CSS and Data Structures.

Supreme Education Foundation Secondary School. September 2013 - June 2016

6 SSCE's grade A - C including Further Math, Math's and English.

Primary School Qualification. 20-2004

First School Leaving Certificate obtained.

Languages:

English. (Professional) Yoruba (Professional) French (Intermediate) Dutch (Amateur)

Interest

I am interested in participating in matters that are not only profitable to me but also to others, lending a hand where it's needed and in my spare time, I enjoy playing basketball, swimming and socializing.

References available on request.